What's going on?
怎麼了？
My eye is a little itchy.
我的眼睛有點癢
Mine too. Yeah.
我的也是
It's really red. You should go see my eye doctor.
你的眼睛好紅喔 你應該去看我的眼科醫生
I'm not gonna see your ex-boyfriend.
理查？我才不要 找你的前男友看眼睛
That's all I hear. Richard, Richard, Richard.
理查…一天到晚理查個沒完
Since we've dated, I've said his name twice.
打從我們開始約會以後 我想我只提過兩次他的名字
Okay. So Richard, Richard.
那好，理查、理查
It's not Richard. It's this new guy. He's good.
不是理查啦 我新找的眼科醫生很棒
I'm sorry. I'm not going to an eye doctor.
抱歉，我不去看眼科醫生
-Oh, God. Here we go. -What?
天啊，老毛病又犯了 什麼？
Anytime anything comes close to touching her eye or anyone else's...
每次只要碰到眼睛這檔事 她馬上就...
...she, like, freaks out. Watch.
...避之唯恐不及 注意看
Ross, come on!
羅斯，你別鬧了
I have a weird thing with my eye. Can we not talk about it?
好，我對我的眼睛有怪癖 麻煩別再討論了，行嗎？
好吧…
Hey,Rach. You know that great song? "Me, Myself and Eye."
瑞秋，還記得有首很棒的歌 我、我自己和… （「我」和「眼睛」同音）
Monica! Come on!
摩妮卡，別鬧啦
All those in favor of getting lunch, say, "eye."
有沒有人想吃午餐？ 有意願的請說…
Ross! Stop it!
羅斯，拜託別鬧了啦
How much did I love The King and Eye?
我有多喜歡「國王與我」？
Chandler!
錢德！
Me too, me too!
我也是…
Just stop it! That's enough!
夠了，別玩了…
-You okay there, man? -Yeah. I got too excited.
你還好吧？ 對，我真的戳到了
The One with Joey's Big Break
本集播出：「眼病難醫」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I gotta go. I'm taking Ben to the park.
先走了，我要帶班去公園
-Give him a kiss for me. -All right. Bye.
幫我親一下他 好，再見
Later.
再見…
I'm so sorry you got caught in the middle of that.
很抱歉讓你們夾在中間尷尬
I didn't mean to be so out there, but I am furious with him.
我也不是故意這麼誇張 但我真的很生他的氣
Calm down?
別激動
I'm trying. Man, that guy can push my buttons!
我在克制 但一想到那個人我就有氣
Why are you so mad?
你幹嘛那麼氣他？
-I don't wanna talk about it. -lt seems like
我不想談，好嗎？ 只是…
You wanna be on my list too? Keep talking.
你想榜上有名就繼續說啊
Has anyone seen my list, by the way?
對了，誰有看到我的黑名單？
No. What's it look like?
沒看到，長什麼樣子？
-A piece of paper and it says, "Ross." -I see.
就是張紙，上頭寫了「羅斯」  瞭解
I just got off the phone with Estelle. Guess what?
我剛和艾斯黛講完電話 你們猜怎麼了？
I got the lead in a movie!!!
我要當電影主角了！
You got the lead in a movie? What's it about?
你要演電影主角，太厲害了 是什麼電影？
It's called Shutterspeed. It's really cool.
片名是「極限速度」， 超酷的
I meet this girl in the subway and we fall in love in, like, a day.
我在地鐵遇見一個女孩 一天之內墜入情網
And then she disappears. But I find out where she lives.
後來她消失無蹤 但我找出了她住在哪裡
This old lady answers the door. I say,"Where's Betsy?"
一個老太太出來開門 我問她「貝絲在哪裡？」
And she says, "Betsy's been dead for 10 years."
她說「貝絲已經過世十年了」
Chilling!
好寒
The best part is,we're filming in the desert outside of Vegas.
最棒的部分是 拍片地點在賭城外的沙漠
-You know what that means. -I know.
兄弟，你知道那是啥意思 對，我知道
Road trip! We can rent a car. I have to be there by Tuesday.
開車殺過去，我們可以租車 我週二以前到那裡就行了
Wait! My grandmother's dead.
等等，我祖母過世了
We can talk about that too,Phoebe.
菲比，我們也可以聊聊那件事
No, her cab.
不…我是說她的計程車
She probably won't be using it. Drive it to Las Vegas.
她八成用不到了 你們可以開去賭城
All right! Thanks!
好耶，菲比，謝了
What are we gonna do about my job?
等等… 那我的工作怎麼辦？
Not go.
別去了
Great! Road trip,baby!
好耶！棒！上路羅！
Is this okay?
你沒意見吧？
Chandler, you don't have to ask for my permission.
錢德，你不用徵求我的允許…
You can go.
我讓你去 謝謝
Rach, we'll be late for the eye doctor.
瑞秋，快點，我們看醫生要遲到了
All right. Let's get this over with.
好啦，早去早解脫
Look what I did.
糟糕，我真是笨手笨腳的
I mean, look at this mess.
搞得一團亂
We're gonna probably have to clean this up.
我得先來清理一下
I mean, we're gonna have to reschedule!
看診時間得要重約了
If you thought that this mess was gonna bother me, you are wrong!
若你認為這點髒亂就會影響我 那你就錯了
All right, let's go, Blinky.
我們走吧，眨眼姑娘
錢德！
「中央咖啡館」
Hey,Joey. What's up?
喬伊 你怎麼了？
I can't decide which route to take to Vegas.
我無法決定走哪條路去賭城
You've traveled a lot, right?
你去過不少地方吧？
Yeah,I've been around.
對，見過世面
Which route should I take? The north or the south route?
那我該選哪一條？ 北線還是南線？
If you take the north route, there's a man with a beard of bees.
走北線途經伊利諾州 有個男人會用蜜蜂當鬍子
Great! Problem solved!
太棒了，問題解決
On the south route, there's a chicken that plays tic-tac-toe.
但是走南線的話 可以看會玩井字遊戲的雞
Well, back to square one.
又回到原點了
I know a way that you can decide.
我知道有個方法能讓你做決定
I'll ask you a series of questions and you answer as quickly as you can.
我會問你一連串的問題 你回答得越快越好
Yes!
好！
Good. But wait.
很好，不過先別急
Here we go. I want you to relax.
開始羅，你先放輕鬆
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸一口氣
Clear your mind.
心裡不要想事情
-Peanut butter or egg whites? -Peanut butter.
花生醬和蛋白，你喜歡哪個？ 花生醬
-Be a fireman or a swimmer? -Swimmer.
你比較想當消防員還是游泳選手? 游泳選手
-You'd sleep with Monica or Rachel? -Monica.
摩妮卡和瑞秋 你比較想跟誰上床？ 摩妮卡…
I always thought it'd be Rachel.
我一直都以為會是瑞秋呢
-No thinking. Tie or ascot? -Ascot.
不要想事情… 領帶或領巾？ 領巾
-North or south route? -North.
南線或北線？ 北線
Bam! There you go! Huh?
答案出現，厲害吧
That was incredible! Beard of bees here I come!
不可思議 蜜蜂胡，我來羅
This guy again.
這傢伙又來了
Hey,what's up?
你好嗎？
Not much. Wanna see a movie tonight?
普通，今晚想看電影嗎？
What do you wanna see?
好啊，你要看什麼？
I don't know.
不知道…
I know how to decide. Show him your game.
我知道我們要如何決定 菲比，讓他見識你的遊戲
No, thank you.
免了，多謝
What's with her?
她是怎麼了？
I don't know. I know how we can decide.
不知道，但我知道怎麼決定了
I'm gonna ask you questions and you answer real quick.
我問你問題，你要很快回答 好
-Action or comedy? -Action.
動作片或喜劇 你比較喜歡哪一個？ 動作片
Who would you rather sleep with, Monica or Rachel?
摩妮卡和瑞秋 你比較想跟誰上床？
Dude, you are sick.
老兄，你真變態
I'm sorry. I forgot you had that whole Rachel thing.
抱歉，我忘了你迷戀過瑞秋
Oh, my God. What does that thing do?
天啊，這是幹嘛的？
-An eye removal machine. -I'm out of here.
這是眼球摘除機 好了，我要走了
I'm kidding.
開玩笑的啦…
Rachel,I'm Dr. Miller.
瑞秋，我是米勒醫生
Monica said you were nervous. Everything will be fine.
摩妮卡說你有點緊張 不過別擔心，不會有事的
-So we're done. -Almost, but first we gotta start.
那就結束吧 快了，不過我們要先開始
This is a glaucoma test. Sit down.
這是青光眼測試 請坐
Put your chin here.
把臉頰放在這裡
Now, you'll feel a small puff of air in each eye.
好，眼睛會有風吹的感覺
What?
什麼？
A small puff of air. Now, come on!
一點點的風啦，你快點！
Here we go.
來羅 好
One,two,three.
一、二、三…
I'm sorry. All right.
抱歉…好吧
I'm gonna stay in here this time.
我這次不會動
Ready?
好了嗎？
-One,two -I'm sorry.
一、二… 抱歉
You know what? I'm gonna hold her head.
我來抓她頭好了
That's okay.
好
一、二…
I'm sorry.
對不起
You're young. You don't have glaucoma.
你還年輕，應該沒有青光眼
So it was very, very nice to meet you, sir.
太好了，很高興認識您
What are you? Are you crazy?
你在幹嘛？你瘋了不成？
You got a small, minor infection in that left eye.
好，你的左眼有些微感染
Take these drops for a week and you'll be as good as new.
這眼藥水一天點三次 連續一周你就宛如新生了
No, I don't put things in my eye.
我不把任何東西放進眼睛裡
We'll see you here in three months. And I'll fit you for a glass eye.
那好吧，三個月後再見 太棒了 我到時幫你裝上義眼
Give me the damn drops!
好啦，把那死眼藥水給我
Dr. Miller?
米勒醫生？
P-E-C-F-D.
P、E、C、F、D
Very good, Monica!
摩妮卡，棒極了
-You know where they are. -I sure do.
你知道獎品放在哪裡 我當然知道
And you don't get one.
你沒有！
You know,those eye drops are a miracle.
那眼藥水實在是太神奇了
My eye is 100 percent better.
我的眼睛百分之百好了
-They're still in my coat. -Damn!
眼藥水還放在我的外套裡 可惡
-You ready to go? -Yeah.
準備好上路了沒？  好了
How cold will it be there? Will all these sweater vests be enough?
不過那邊會有多冷？ 我要帶外套 還是帶這些毛衣就夠了？
-What? -I love you.
怎麼了？ 我愛你
I wish Ross was coming with us. I'll miss him.
真希望羅斯也能一起去 我一定會很想念他的
Thanks. I just got that jerk out of my mind.
真是多謝你了 我才剛把那個混蛋給忘掉
Is the movie putting us up in a big hotel suite?
我們住哪裡？ 電影公司招待的飯店大套房？
Not really. It's an independent film.
不算是，這是獨立製片的電影
We don't have a big budget. I'll stay in your room.
沒有大預算 我想我住你房間好了
Once you get paid, you'll be springing for a suite.
瞭解，但等你拿到酬勞之後 你會請我住飯店大套房吧？
They must be paying you a lot.
主演電影的片酬一定不少吧？
Yeah. For every dollar Shutterspeed makes...
是啊，我算給你聽 「極限速度」每賺一塊錢
...one penny of it goes right in Joey's pocket.
喬伊就能分到百分之一
You don't get paid unless it makes money?
所以電影賺錢你才有錢拿？
Did you not hear the plot of the movie?
你不知道這電影的情節嗎？
"She's been dead for 10 years."
「貝絲已經過世十年了」
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
我就快變成百萬富翁了
I wanted to say goodbye.
我只是要來跟你們說個再見
And to see if you guys would place a little bet for me.
順便托你們幫我下個注
Twenty bucks on black 15.
20美元押黑色15號
-You got it! -All right.
沒問題 好
-You remember the number,right? -Yeah,black 13.
你記得號碼吧？ 記得，黑色13號
-Black 15! -You got it.
黑色15號啦! 沒問題
-All right. Bye-bye,now. -Bye,you guys.
再見…
I'll say bye at the car.
我去車子那裡替你送行
Anyone wanna say bye to me at the car?
誰要去車子那裡替我送行？
I'll say goodbye to you at the car if you don't mind the pus.
我可以替你送行 只要你不介意我眼睛化膿
See you!
再見
But wait a minute. The pus is good. It means it's healing.
等等，化膿是好現象 表示快要好了
Hey, Phoebe. What you reading?
菲比，你在看什麼？
菲比？
Hello?
菲比？…
Come on!
菲比？別鬧了啦
I'm sorry, I didn't see you there.
抱歉，我不知道你在這裡
Phoebe, are you mad at me or something?
菲比，你在生我的氣嗎？
If you are, please tell me what it is I did.
我做了什麼讓你生氣的事？
-lf you don't know, I can't help you. -I don't know.
你不知道，我也幫不了你 我是不知道啊
Well, I can't help you.
那我也無能為力了
Well, whatever it is, I am very, very sorry. Okay?
不管是什麼事，我都非常抱歉
Apology accepted.
我接受你的道歉
So we're good?
那我們沒事了？
好吧
I'll see you later,okay?
那晚點見羅
Bye,fat-ass.
好，大屁股
All right!
夠了！
Will you please tell me what it is that made you so mad at me?
菲比，你快點說 我做了什麼讓你這麼不爽？
I don't know! I don't remember!
我不知道，我不記得了
What do you mean, you can't remember?
什麼叫做你不記得了？
I was so focused on being mad at you, I forgot what it was I was mad about.
我太專心在生你的氣 氣到都忘了生氣的原因
If you can't remember, can't we just forget about this?
既然忘了，那能不能就算了？
Oh,no. I am mad at you. I know that much.
不行，我生你的氣，這很確定
But I'm sorry about the fat-ass thing because you have a sweet, little heinie.
但我很抱歉罵你大屁股 因為你的小屁屁很可愛
I'm getting pretty tired. You'll have to take over soon.
我開得好累，你隨時準備接手
We've been driving for a half-hour. You haven't looked at the road once.
我們才上路半小時 而且你都沒在看路
Don't worry. It's out there.
別擔心，路就是路嘛
Maybe I just need lunch. You wanna eat?
我想我該吃午飯了 是啊 你要吃嗎？
My treat.
我請客
Isn't that Ross' money?
那不是羅斯的錢嗎？
Ross' treat. Where do you wanna eat?
是啊，好吧，羅斯請客 你想吃什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道
I know how we can decide.
我知道要怎麼決定了
I'll ask you questions.
我問你一堆問題
And then you have to answer real fast.
你得很快回答
So clear your mind. Clear it right out. Clear it out.
不要想事情，什麼都不要想 好
It's all clear except for this image of a small, purple lamp.
我沒在想事情 但心裡有個小紫燈的形象
Is that all right if that stays in there?
這樣不礙事吧？
I don't see why not. I guess.
應該不礙事吧…
You have to answer with the first thing that pops into your head, okay?
想到什麼就直接回答 好
-Would you rather be too wet or too dry? -Too dry.
你寧願太濕或太干？ 太干
-Do you believe in ghosts? -No.
你相不相信有鬼？ 不相信
-Will this movie be my big break? -No.
這電影會讓我翻身嗎？ 不會
-What? -Yes.
什麼？ 會
-Dude,you said,no. -I also said,yes.
你剛才說不會 我也說了會啊
-This won't be my big break? -No.
你不覺得我這次會翻身？ 對
I don't believe this.
豈有此理
Look, I just don't want you to get your hopes up too high.
喬伊，我只是不要你期望太高
What are you talking about? I'm the lead in a movie!
你在胡說什麼？ 我是電影主角耶！
They're not even paying you! This doesn't sound like a real movie!
那他們還不付你片酬？ 這電影聽來跟幌子一樣
I don't know why you're dumping all over my big break.
我不需要聽這種話 搞不懂你幹嘛洩我的氣
I don't think this is gonna be your big break.
喬伊，我不認為你這次能翻身
Are you on this trip to make me feel like a loser?
所以你才來這趟？ 讓我覺得自己是窩囊廢？
-I'd rather be alone. -You don't want me here?
如果是這樣，那我寧願自己去
Not if you're like this.
你不要我陪你去？ 你這樣我不要也罷
The next time you ask me a question like that,I'll lie.
那好吧，下次你再問那種問題 我騙你就是了
I don't want you on the trip.
對！我不要你一起去
Why don't you pull over. I'll get out now.
好，無所謂… 你停車，我馬上走
Fine.
好啊
Get out.
滾吧
You can't stop on a bridge.
在橋上不能隨便就停車
-Get out! -Fine!
滾啦！ 好啦！
Wait! Wait! There's no sidewalk!
等等…橋上沒有人行道！
Yeah. I'm gonna die here.
我一定會死在這裡
「中央咖啡館」
Are you mad at me because my hair gel smells?
好，你生我的氣 是因為我發膠有怪味？
不是
Because I said your handwriting is childlike?
你生我的氣 是因為我說你寫字像小孩？
No. That made me feel precious.
不是，這樣才特別啊
Because he's always correcting people's grammar?
我知道了 因為他老愛糾正別人文法？
"Whom, whom." Sometimes it's "who"!
什麼「WHOM」個沒完 有時候是用「WHO」啦！
Yeah? Sometimes it's:
是嗎？有時候是…
Did you beat him at a board game? He's such a baby when he loses.
還是你玩西洋棋贏了他？ 他開始居於劣勢就很孩子氣
Okay, I'm the baby.
好，我孩子氣
Hey! Stop it!
住手！
What are you doing here?
錢德，你怎麼會在這裡？
Joey kicked me out of the car on the bridge.
喬伊在華盛頓大橋上 把我趕下車
-Why? -I don't know. He went crazy.
為什麼？… 不知道，他突然發飆
We played that game where you ask questions and answer fast.
我們在玩快問快答的遊戲
That game should not be played without my supervision.
沒有我在場監督 絕對不能玩那個遊戲
I don't know what made him mad.
我不知道他幹嘛氣成那樣
All I said was that this wouldn't be his big break...
我只是說他這次不會翻身
...that it wouldn't do anything for him...
說這部電影幫不了他
...and that it didn't sound real.
說這部電影很像是幌子
Okay, he should've pushed me off the bridge.
好啦，他該把我推下橋才對
What's in the bag?
你袋子裡有什麼？
I figured you'd be mad at me...
我猜想你們大家也會對我不爽
...so I got gifts that I found on the roadside.
所以我在路邊檢了些禮物
-Who wants the one-legged teddy bear? -I do!
誰要一條腿的泰迪熊？ 我要
來了
-Not even close. -I need help! I can't do this.
差遠了 好啦，你幫我，我沒辦法
Come on. Let's do it.
來，我幫你
Sit down. All right, put your head back.
坐下 好 頭往後仰 好
-Now open your eyes. -Okay,they are.
把眼睛張開 好，張開了
-How many fingers am I holding up? -Four.
我舉了幾隻手指頭？ 四隻
I was thinking four.
天啊，我心裡想的也是四隻
-Really? -Yes!
真的？ 是啊
Why don't we start with a practice one.
這樣吧，我們先來預演一次 好
-No drops. -Great!
不滴眼藥水 太好了
On three. One,two,three.
數到三，一、二、三…
My pillow's all wet!
你害我沙發枕都濕了
Well,you said it was practice!
你自己說是預演的
Why did you move?
那你幹嘛動？
I knew you were lying!
因為我知道你在騙我
-Come here. -What are you doing?
好吧，過來 你要幹嘛？
Stop it! Oh,my God!
摩妮卡，天啊！住手！…
I am going....
我要…
Turn it over!
轉回來！
I am going to get...
我要把...
...get these drops in your eye.
把眼藥水…滴進你眼睛
Oh, my God! You really are freakishly strong.
天啊，你蠻力真大
Stop! Stop!
摩妮卡，住手！…
Stop it!
住手
Damn,it's empty!
可惡，滴完了！
If Joey and Chandler walked in now, we could make a fortune.
如果現在喬伊和錢德走進來 我們就發了
That is definitely Chandler, Joey or Ross.
一定是錢德、喬伊或羅斯
Or Rachel.
或是瑞秋
It's Joey.
喂？ 是喬伊
Chandler told me what happened. He's really upset.
真高興你打來 錢德都說了，他很難過
Not as upset as he'll be when he finds out what I did with his sweater vests.
等他知道他毛衣的下場 他一定會更難過
What did you do to them?
你把他的毛衣怎麼了？
There's a well-dressed pack of dogs in Ohio.
這麼說吧，在俄亥俄州 有一夥打扮亮麗的狗
I gotta ask Phoebe something about the car.
摩妮卡？菲比在嗎？ 我有車子的事要問她
Hold on one second.
她在，你等等
-Hey, dude. -Hey, Phoebe.
嗨 嗨，菲比，你聽我說
This wooden box keeps sliding out. What is it?
座位底下有個木盒滑出來 那是什麼？
My grandma.
那是我祖母
And thanks. She's having a great time.
喬伊，謝謝你，她玩得很愉快
Is that Joey? Let me talk to him.
是喬伊嗎？我要跟他說…
Chandler's here. He was wondering if
喬伊？錢德不知道你…
I guess he ran out of change.
我想他零錢正好用完了
How am I gonna apologize to him if he won't even talk to me?
他連話都不想跟我說 這樣我要怎麼跟他道歉？
Send him something. So when he gets there, he'll know you're sorry.
或許你應該寄點東西給他 等他到了賭城 就知道你想表達歉意了
That's a good idea. I wonder where I could get a basket of porn?
好主意，上哪兒找一堆A片？
No,don't say, "I'm sorry," with porn.
不行，不能用A片道歉啦 真的？
You should send him a carton of cigarettes.
你應該寄一條煙過去
Because that way he can trade it for protection.
他可以用來換取保護
No. That's prison.
錯了，監獄裡才是這樣
I know how we're gonna figure this out.
菲比，我知道要怎麼找出原因
Clear your mind...
好，什麼都不要想
...and answer the first thing that comes into your head.
想到什麼就直接回答
-Do you like flora or fauna? -Fauna.
你比較喜歡植物還是動物？ 動物
-Simon or Garfunkel? -Garfunkel.
你想當賽門還是葛芬柯？ 葛芬柯
-Why are you mad? -You said I was boring.
你為何生我的氣？ 因為你說我很無趣
When did I say that?
我何時說過你無趣了？
Oh,my God! I remember now! We were playing chess.
天啊，我想起來了 我們下西洋棋那次
Phoebe,you and l have never played chess.
菲比，我和你沒下過西洋棋
Remember that time on the frozen lake? We were playing. You said I was boring.
有啦，記得冰凍湖那次嗎？ 我們玩西洋棋，你說我很無趣
Then you took off your energy mask and you were Cameron Diaz.
然後你脫下面具 變成了卡麥蓉狄亞
There's a chance this may have been a dream.
好吧，這有可能是夢境
So this entire time,you've been angry with me because of a dream?
所以你這陣子以來對我不爽 全是因為一場夢？
Well, guess what, now I'm mad at you.
菲比，現在輪我不爽你了
I wanted to make sure this wasn't a dream.
我想確定這次不是作夢
Otherwise we're wasting our time.
免得浪費彼此的時間
Stanley!
史丹利！
Your leading man is here. Let's get to work.
你的主角來了，咱們開工吧
Slight change of plans.
計劃有些改變
We've shut down.
我們停拍了
What? Why?
什麼？為什麼？
It's a money thing. We don't have any.
我們沒錢
You're kidding, right?
你在開玩笑吧？ 不是
What?
什麼？
It's probably just temporary.
這或許只是暫時的
We're hoping to get some money soon. Just hang out.
我們希望能快點籌到資金 你先撐一下
Hang out? How long?
撐一下？要撐多久？
I don't know. A week. Maybe two. The money will turn up.
不知道，一、兩個星期吧 資金會出現的
People always wanna invest in movies. You're not rich?
大家都愛投資拍電影 你該不會是有錢人吧？ 我不是
Worth a shot.
問一下也無妨
Well, Joey, let me know where you're staying,okay?
喬伊，讓我知道你在哪兒落腳
Hey, pal. Are you Joey Tribbiani?
你是喬伊崔比亞尼嗎？ 我是
These got left for you.
這是有人留給你的
Thanks.
謝了
"Congratulations on your big break."
恭喜你翻身了
-Monica, it's Joey. -Hey,Joey.
喂？ 摩妮卡，我是喬伊
You remember me even though you're a star.
你當了大明星還是記得我
Come on. It'll be years before I forget you.
得了吧，忘記你也要好幾年
What's it like on a movie set?
拍片現場是什麼樣子？
Do you have a dressing room and a chair with your name?
你有自己的更衣室嗎？ 有專屬的私人座椅嗎？
Yeah,yeah,I got all that going on.
有啊，一切都在進行當中
Tell Chandler he couldn't have been more wrong.
你一定要跟錢德說 他完完全全看走眼了
I gotta go,Monica. My sushi's here.
摩妮卡，我得掛了 我的壽司送來了
Sorry about that. Thanks for waiting.
抱歉，多謝你們等我 沒關係
Everybody smile.
大家笑一個，多謝
Thanks a lot. Enjoy your stay at Caesars. We hope it's toga-rific.
希望你們在凱薩住得愉快 祝福你們「羅馬」精神
Kill me. Kill me now.
殺了我吧…
Rach, can you pass me the TV Guide?
瑞秋，電視指南遞給我好嗎？ 好啊
Go!
上！
What are you doing? Get off! Oh, my God!
住手！…天啊！
Hold it open. Okay.
好了…
We'll see you in about three or four hours.
三、四個小時後再見